Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Payments to creditors of national banks placed in receivership during 1931-39. Prepared by Mark D'Elia and Clark Warburton. (Folder 9-12, Box 89)
  - Relation to suspended to active national banks, 1921-33. (Folder 13, Box 89)
  - Memoranda, September 1946. (Folder 14, Box 89)
  - Memoranda, January 1948- December 1952. (Folder 15-68, Box 89)
  - Joint Committee on the Economic Report- Questionnaire and FDIC Answers. (Folder 1, 2, Box 90)
  - Some Considerations Bearing on Increased Deposit Insurance Coverage. (Folder 3, Box 90)
  - The Purpose of Insurance of Accounts in Savings Institutions. (Folder 5, Box 90)
  - The Deposit Insurance Legislation of 1933. (Folder 6, Box 90)
  - Actuarial Data Relevant to Deposit Insurance. (Folder 7, Box 90)
  - Correspondence- An increase in interest rates, December 1956. (Folder 8, Box 90)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation- Miscellaneous, materials. (Folder 9a, 9b, Box 90)
  - FDIC, pay off cases- Accounts and depositors. (Folder 10, Box 90)
  - Insurance Coverage- Suggested increase. 9-22-62 (Folder 11, Box 90)
  - Memoranda. (Folder 12, Box 90)
  - Liquidation Division. (Folder 13, Box 90)
  - Questionnaire- Monetary and Banking Policy. (Folder 14, Box 90)
  - Deposit Insurance Fund. (Folder 15, Box 90)
  - Adequacy of FDIC Fund- Correspondence. (Folder 16, Box 90)
  - Selected income and expense data, insured commercial banks, 1947-54. (Folder 17, Box 90)
  - Accounts in excess of $100,000, 1936-41. (Folder 18, Box 90)
  - Deposit insurance. (Folder 19, Box 90)
  - The Insurance of Bank Deposits by Irvin Bussing, 1938. (Folder 20, Box 90)
  - Report on the Federal Reserve Board by George L. Bach, 1948. (Folder 21, Box 90)
  - Regulation of the Maximum Interest Rate Payable on Deposits. (Folder 22, Box 90)
  - Prohibition of Interest on Demand Deposits. (Folder 23, Box 90)
  - Absorptions- ABS 0000 T. (Folder 1, Box 92)
  - Department of Agriculture- AGR 0000 T. (Folder 2, Box 92)
  - All Bank Statistical Data - ALL 0000 T. (Folder 3, Box 92)
  - American Banker. (Folder 4, Box 92)
  - American Bankers Association, 1936-60 - AME 0100 T. (Folder 5-7, Box 92)
  - American Bankers Association State Taxation Study- AME 01010 T. (Folder 8, Box 92)
  - American Economic Association- AME 0200 T. (Folder 9, Box 92)
  - American Industrial Bankers Association- AME 04000 T. (Folder 11, Box 92)
  - American Institute of Banking- AME 05000 T. (Folder 12, Box 92)
  - American Statistical Association- AME 06000 T. (Folder 13, Box 92)
  - Emergency Preparedness. (Folder 14, Box 92)
  - Files Management - AM 10-3. (Folder 15, Box 92)
  - Annual Report- PRI 6-1. (Folder 16, Box 92)
  - Buildings and grounds. (Folder 17, Box 92)
  - Application for admission to deposit insurance- APP 00000 T. (Folder 18, Box 92)
  - Assessments, 1934-46 - ASS 00000 T. (Folder 19-21, Box 92)
  - Reduction in assessment rate. (Folder 22, Box 92)
  - Assessments, 1947-59- ASS 00000 T. (Folder 1, 2, Box 93)
  - Audit of FDIC- AUD 00000 T. (Folder 3, 4, Box 93)
  - Automatic Data Processing- FDIC Committee to Study ADP and Interagency Committee, 1957-62- AUT 00000 T. (Folder 5-8, Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 1, Box 94)
  - Capital- Illinois Bankers Association, NBER study, ratios of capital accounts to assets, etc. (Folder 2-4, Box 94)
  - Central files index. (Folder 5, Box 94)
  - Department of Commerce. (Folder 6, Box 94)
  - Commerce, Bureau of Census (Folder 7, Box 94)
  - Commission on Money and Credit. (Folder 8, Box 94)
  - Committee- Library, 1942-64, National Agricultural Credit, and Administration. (Folder 9, 10, 11, 15, Box 94)
  - Depository Libraries. (Folder 12, Box 94)
  - Conference- not included in central files index. (Folder 13, Box 94)
  - PRI 4-3-2 Congress. (Folder 14, Box 94)
  - Competition in Banking. (Folder 16, Box 94)
  - Comptroller of the Currency. (Folder 17, Box 94)
  - Consumer Instalment Financing- Study by Ernst A. Dauer. (Folder 18, Box 94)
  - Council of the Economic Advisors. (Folder 19, Box 94)
  - Dedication of FDIC Building in 1963. (Folder 1, Box 95)
  - Defalcations, the insured banks, charts, speeches, articles, recoveries in closed insured banks, and insured banks receiving financial aid from the FDIC, 1946-1952. (Folder 2-6, Box 95)
  - Certificate of deposit. (Folder 7, Box 95)
  - Disclosure Law, S. 1642. (Folder 8, Box 95)
  - Deposits, insured by FDIC (Estimates). (Folder 9, Box 95)
  - Earnings, Bank. (Folder 10, Box 95)
  - Economists with banks. 8-10-60 (Folder 11, Box 95)
  - Examiner, research and statistics data distributed to. (Folder 12, Box 95)
  - Examiner training program. (Folder 13, Box 95)
  - Farm credit administration. (Folder 14, Box 95)
  - FDIC Act. (Folder 15, Box 95)
  - Banking Act of 1933. (Folder 16, Box 95)
  - Annual Reports- Federal Credit Union, 1941-1947. (Folder 17, Box 95)
  - Executive order no.9148- Assumption of Administration of Federal Credit Union by the FDIC. (Folder 18, Box 95)
  - H.R. 2385 and H.R. 3327 to amend Federal Credit Act. (Folder 19, Box 95)
  - S. 2225- A bill to transfer administration of the Federal Credit Union Act to the Federal Security Agency. (Folder 20, Box 95)
  - Annual Report- Federal Credit Union. (Folder 21, Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous. (Folder 22, Box 95)
  - FDIC, Districts- Identical letters to each district. (Folder 23, Box 95)
  - FDIC, Financial Statements 1964-1966. (Folder 24, Box 95)
  - Ohio- Ayres' correspondence regarding "This Business Relapse", 1934-1938. (Folder 1, Box 96)
  - New York- 1934-1944, 1945-1951, correspondence of Edison H. Cramer 1940-1958, correspondence to 1959-1964, and New York state study of banking facilities by Donald H. Davenport. (Folder 2-6, Box 96)
  - North Carolina, correspondence to 1949-1964. (Folder 7, Box 96)
  - North Dakota, correspondence to 1939-1962. (Folder 8, Box 96)
  - Ohio, correspondence to 1939-1964. (Folder 9, Box 96)
  - Oklahoma, correspondence to 1949-1964. (Folder 10, Box 96)
  - Oregon, correspondence to 1949-1964. (Folder 11, Box 96)
  - Pennsylvania, correspondence to 1939-1964. (Folder 12, Box 96)
  - South Carolina, correspondence to 1949-1966. (Folder 13, Box 96)
  - South Dakota, correspondence to 1939-1962. (Folder 14, Box 96)
  - Tennessee, correspondence to 1938-1963. (Folder 15, Box 96)
  - Texas, correspondence to 1937-1963. (Folder 16, Box 96)
  - William E. Koenker. (Folder 17, Box 96)
  - Business Equipment Manufacturers Association- NYC (Mrs. G. L. Meyer) 1957-1963. (Folder 18, Box 96)
  - New York- Bankers Trust Company, correspondence to 1936-1960. (Folder 1, Box 97)
  - Connecticut, correspondence to 1943-1960. (Folder 2, Box 97)
  - Colorado, correspondence to 1934-1964. (Folder 3, Box 97)
  - District of Colombia, correspondence to 1936-1963. (Folder 4, Box 97)
  - Brookings Institution, Washington D.C. 1934-1959. (Folder 5, Box 97)
  - Delaware, correspondence to 1942-1962. (Folder 6, Box 97)
  - Georgia, correspondence to 1943-1964. (Folder 7, Box 97)
  - Hawaii, correspondence to 1964. (Folder 8, Box 97)
  - Illinois, correspondence to 1936-1964, Ernst A. Dauer 1935-1952, and 1951-1966. (Folder 9-11, Box 97)
  - Iowia, correspondence to 1951-1964. (Folder 12, Box 97)
  - Kansas, correspondence to 1948-1963. (Folder 13, Box 97)
  - Kentucky, correspondence to 1959-1960. (Folder 14, Box 97)
  - Florida, correspondence to 1949-1964. (Folder 15, Box 97)
  - Louisiana, correspondence to 1951-1963. (Folder 16, Box 97)
  - Maine, correspondence to 1952-1962. (Folder 17, Box 97)
  - Maryland, correspondence to 1937-1964. (Folder 18, Box 97)
  - Massachusetts, correspondence to, 1936-1964. (Folder 19, Box 97)
  - Michigan, correspondence to 1950-1964. (Folder 20, Box 97)
  - Minnesota, correspondence to 1935-1964 and Northwest Bancorporation 1941-1963. (Folder 21, 22, Box 97)
  - Mississippi, correspondence to 1949-1959. (Folder 23, Box 97)
  - Missouri, correspondence to 1936-1964. (Folder 24, Box 97)
  - Montana, correspondence to 1945-1964. (Folder 25, Box 97)
  - Nebraska, correspondence to 1934-1963. (Folder 26, Box 97)
  - New Hampshire, correspondence to 1945-1963. (Folder 27, Box 97)
  - New Jersey, correspondence to 1939-1964. (Folder 28, Box 97)
  - New Mexico, correspondence to 1949-1961. (Folder 29, Box 97)
  - New York, Irving Trust Company 1935-1948. (Folder 30, Box 97)
  - Nevada, correspondence to 1957-1962. (Folder 31, Box 97)
  - Utah, correspondence to 1941-1963. (Folder 1, Box 98)
  - Vermont, correspondence to 1948-1962. (Folder 2, Box 98)
  - Virginia, correspondence to 1935-1964. (Folder 3, Box 98)
  - Washington, correspondence to 1948-1963. (Folder 4, Box 98)
  - West Virginia, correspondence to 1936-1963. (Folder 5, Box 98)
  - Wisconsin, correspondence to 1943-1964. (Folder 6, Box 98)
  - Wyoming, correspondence to 1950-1951. (Folder 7, Box 98)
  - Foreign correspondence to 1950-1964. (Folder 8, Box 98)
  - FDIC- Opinion survey, correspondence to 1948, news, retirement, and rules and regulations. (Folder 9, 10, 11, 15, Box 98)
  - Federal Reserve Banks, 1935-1963. (Folder 12, Box 98)
  - Identical letters to each bank. (Folder 13, Box 98)
  - Canada, correspondence to 1938-1953. (Folder 14, Box 98)
  - Federal Housing Administration. (Folder 16, Box 98)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board. (Folder 17, Box 98)
  - Federal Employees- Health benefits 1952-1962, group life insurance 1954-1960, and compensation act 1940-1950. (Folder 18-20, Box 98)
  - Federal Reserve System- correspondence to 1936-1944, 1945-1949, 1950-54, 1955-1960, agricultural loan system 1956, agricultural loan surveys 1947, 1951. (Folder 21-27, Box 98)
  - Federal Reserve System- Bach Regulatory on FRB(for CURA) and FDIC comments 1948, by committee on independent regulating commissions 1948, annual report 1938, an agricultural loan system 1966. (Folder 1-4, Box 99)
  - Federal Savings and Loan Insurance Corporation 1936-1938. (Folder 5, Box 99)
  - Fidelity Bond Coverage- Correspondence and memoranda. (Folder 6, Box 99)
  - Financial Control of Government Corporations. (Folder 7, Box 99)
  - Financial Institutions Act 1957-1966. (Folder 8, Box 99)
  - Foreign Visitors 1956- 1964. (Folder 9, Box 99)
  - Foreign Benefits- Division study 1953-1954. (Folder 10, Box 99)
  - General Accounting Office 1951-1964. (Folder 11, Box 99)
  - General Public 1964-1966. (Folder 12, Box 99)
  - Civil Service Commission 1937-1940. (Folder 13, Box 99)
  - Legislative Reference Service 1955-1956. (Folder 14, Box 99)
  - Government Agencies- Miscellaneous 1939-1954. (Folder 15, Box 99)
  - Hardy, Charles O.- Lectures outline, lectures on Money and Banking Vol. I-II. (Folder 1-3, Box 100)
  - History of Banking in Colorado 1876-1946 Seventy Years of Progress by Fred R. Niehaus. (Folder 4, Box 100)
  - History of Banking in Iowa- Banking Progress in Iowa 1934-1951. (Folder 5, Box 100)
  - House of Representatives 1934-1943,1944-1953, 1954-1963. (Folder 6, 7, 14, Box 100)
  - Hoover Committee 1947-1965. (Folder 8, Box 100)
  - Interest Rates- Regulation on time deposits 1934-1945, 1960-1962. (Folder 9, 10, Box 100)
  - Insurance, Bank- Obligation 1936-1963. (Folder 11, Box 100)
  - Independent Bankers Association 1947-1963. (Folder 12, Box 100)
  - Incentive Awards 1962. (Folder 13, Box 100)
  - Interest rates, maximum paid by insured commercial banks 1965-1966. (Folder 1, Box 101)
  - Interest, absorption of exchange 1957-1964. (Folder 2, Box 101)
  - Operation of Non-Par Banks, 1935-1942- A Statistical Analysis. (Folder 3, Box 101)
  - Interest- Monthly Survey of Conventional Loan Approvals on 1-Family Nonfarm Homes. (Folder 4, Box 101)
  - Service Charge Schedules 1938-1939- State Banks Association A-L, M-Z. (Folder 5, 8, Box 101)
  - Service Corporations, Bank 1962. (Folder 6, Box 101)
  - IOA- Three final assets. (Folder 7, Box 101)
  - Absorption of Exchange Charges- Correspondence with Board of Governors, an analysis of service charges in sixteen states, miscellaneous 1938-1944, and memoranda. (Folder 9-13, Box 101)
  - Bank capital study- Miscellaneous. (Folder 1, Box 102)
  - Bank correspondence 1964-1966. (Folder 2, Box 102)
  - Bank directors' duties 1952. (Folder 3, Box 102)
  - Bank facilities 1935-1964. (Folder 4, Box 102)
  - Bank holding companies 1948, 1954. (Folder 5, Box 102)
  - Bank personnel, salaries- Patman's requests of 1942 and 1953, Fed bank supervisory agencies for ABA 1956-1958, wages and fees, number of offices and employees by state 1941-1942. (Folder 6-8, Box 102)
  - Bank supervision. (Folder 9, Box 102)
  - Banking schools 1952-1953. (Folder 10, Box 102)
  - Bank system- Dual 1943, in Indiana, concentration, branch banking 1962-1965, and investment program. (Folder 11-15, Box 102)
  - Budget Breau. (Folder 16, Box 102)
  - Budget report forms under Federal Reports Act 1938-1964. (Folder 17, Box 102)
  - Bank ownership. (Folder 18, Box 102)
  - Bank capital 1936-1962- Capital problems 1936-1941. (Folder 19, Box 102)
  - Correspondence- Alabama 1964, Arizona 1960, Arkansas 1962, and California 1964. (Folder 1-4, Box 103)
  - California- Bank of America 1934-1964. (Folder 5, Box 103)
  - FDIC- History of Federal deposit, history of legislative, coverage of deposit insurance 1934-1961, Employees Federal Credit Union, employees' fifteen-year pin, employee incentive awards program, and fair employment offices. (Folder 6-12, Box 103)
  - Supervising Examiner- Massachusetts, New York, Ohio, Virginia, Georgia, Missouri, Wisconsin 1934-1962, Illinois 1934-1963, Minnesota 1934-1962, Missouri 1934-1961, Texas, California. (Folder 13-24, Box 103)
  - Addresses. (Folder 25, Box 103)
  - Research and statistics participation in supervising examiners' conferences. (Folder 26, Box 103)
  - Conference of supervising examiners April 22-25, 1946. (Folder 27, Box 103)
  - Absorption of exchange charges- Testimony of chairman FDIC, H.R. 3956. (Folder 1, Box 104)
  - J.C.E.R- 80th Congress (Plan to control inflation 1947-1948), report on hearings, 1954. (Folder 2, 4, 5, 6, Box 104)
  - Joint committee on the Economic Report. (Folder 3, Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 7, Box 104)
  - Department of Justice. (Folder 8, Box 104)
  - Executive Order No. 9112. 3-26-42 (Folder 9, Box 104)
  - Proposed Executive Order, April 1943. (Folder 10, Box 104)
  - H.R. 9682- Revenue Act of 1938. (Folder 11, Box 104)
  - 75th Congress- Beyond committee report. (Folder 12, Box 104)
  - 76th Congress- Legislation. (Folder 13, Box 104)
  - 88th Congress- Federal Banking Legislation. (Folder 14, Box 104)
  - House and Senate Bills Pertaining to Banking. (Folder 15, Box 104)
  - H.R. 5874- A Bill to Establish a Federal Banking 1963. (Folder 16, Box 104)
  - Legislation 1956-1966. (Folder 17, Box 104)
  - H.R. 5220- Regulation of trust indentures 1939. (Folder 1, Box 105)
  - H.R. 10413 (Doughton)- Excess Profits Tax 1940. (Folder 2, Box 105)
  - S. 477- Trust Indentures Act. (Folder 3, Box 105)
  - S. 757- Disposition of unclaimed deposits in national banks. (Folder 4, Box 105)
  - S. 1203- Establish regional industrial banks. (Folder 5, Box 105)
  - S. 1482 (Mead)- RFC insurance of bank loans. (Folder 6, Box 105)
  - S. 1917 to establish a Bank of the U.S., S.1964 authorize charitable contributions by national banking associations, S. 2045 to transfer to FDIC all bank examinations, S. 2343 to provide for the insurance of loans to business. (Folder 7-9, Box 105)
  - Eliminate discrimination between member and non-member banks. (Folder 10, Box 105)
  - To establish Industrial Loan Corporation. (Folder 11, Box 105)
  - Restrict establishment of branch offices by financial institutions. (Folder 12, Box 105)
  - S. 3867- Capital Ratio Bill. (Folder 13, Box 105)
  - Executive K- 77th Congress 1st Session (establish Inter-American Bank). (Folder 14, Box 105)
  - S. Res. 223 (Tydings)- Inquiry regarding transfer of employees. (Folder 15, Box 105)
  - H.R. 3531 (Doughton) to amend certain provisions of internal revenue code relating to excess profits tax, H.R. 10413 excess profit tax 1940, H.R. 3531, H.R. 3565 expenses of examination of national banks. (Folder 16-18, Box 105)
  - H.R. 4646 stabilization fund, H.R. 4674 provides for increasing lending authority of RFC, H.R. 4691 to amend Federal Credit Union Act. (Folder 19, 20, Box 105)
  - H.R. 5417 (Doughton) Revenue Act of 1941, H.R. 6391, H.R. 7378 (Doughton), H.R. 7158 (Steagall), H.R. 7310 (Ford), H.R. 1818 (Ford). (Folder 21-25, Box 105)
  - S. 3839, S. 25, S. 310, S. 939, S. 952, S. 1014, S. 1540, S. 1603, S. 1666, S. 1671, S. 1905, S. 1987, S. 2039, S. 2250, S. 2393, S. 700. (Folder 26-36, Box 105)
  - H.R. 1699, H.R. 2001, H.R. 2634, H.R. 4804, H.R. 5258. (Folder 37, 40, 41, 42, 43, Box 105)
  - S. 923, S. 986, S. 197, S. 678, S. 689, S. 914, S. 985, S. 1041, S. 1341, S. 1769, S. 1777, S. 1892, S. 1918, S. 7(Public Law 404). (Folder 38, 39, 44-52, Box 105)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 53, Box 105)
  - H.R. 53 establishment of branches of national banks, H.R. 591 establishing fund to guarantee loans to businesses, H.R. 2177 relating to bank accounts. (Folder 1, Box 106)
  - H.R. Hearings on Bretton Woods Agreements, H.R. establishment of branches by national banking associations. (Folder 2, 3, Box 106)
  - S. 375 provide effective administration of certain lending agencies of the Federal Government, S. 380 full employment, S. 2822 amend the FDI act. (Folder 4-6, Box 106)
  - Legislation- Section 5219 USRS. (Folder 7, Box 106)
  - Proposed Legislation- 78th Congress 1943. (Folder 8, Box 106)
  - Statements of chairman. (Folder 9, Box 106)
  - H.R. 5357 and S. 1715- Proposed amendments to Section 12B of FR Act. (Folder 10, Box 106)
  - Board of Directors- Chairman's office. (Folder 11, Box 106)
  - Examination Division 1939-1958. (Folder 12, Box 106)
  - Bank Loans 1939-1961. (Folder 13, Box 106)
  - Manpower utilization 1955- 1966. (Folder 14, Box 106)
  - Secretary's office 1934-1957. (Folder 15, Box 106)
  - Publications and Information office 1950-1955. (Folder 16, Box 106)
  - Service Branch 1948-1951. (Folder 17, Box 106)
  - Service Branch 1948-1951. (Folder 17, Box 106)
  - Research and Statistics Division- Duties and functions, research programs, etc. (Folder 18 a, b, Box 106)
  - Research Study- #3 in Money Management by Clark Warburton. (Folder 19, Box 106)
  - Public Relations- Research and Statistics Act. 7-1-40, 6-30-41 (Folder 20, Box 106)
  - Research and Statistics Division- Replies to questionnaire of the Bureau of the Budget. 1-6-43 (Folder 21, Box 106)
  - Research and Statistics Division- Report on work of the Division, requested in memo EO-72. 3-11-46 (Folder 22, Box 106)
  - Statistics Section- Tabulating Machine Sub-Unit- Fees charged for tabulation. (Folder 23, Box 106)
  - Memoranda- Dr. Cramer, Mr. Cresswell, Mr. Hengren, and Mr. Golembe 1951-1960. (Folder 24-27, Box 106)
  - Reports supplementing the "Staff Study of Proposals to Reduce the Assessment Income of the FDIC." (Folder 28, Box 106)
  - Memoranda- Florence Helm 1935-1946, Harry L. Severson 1937-1946, Clark Warburton 1935-1954. (Folder 1-12, Box 107)
  - Warburton- Manuscripts. (Folder 13, Box 107)
  - Mergers 1952-1959. (Folder 14, Box 107)
  - Mergers- Insured banks receiving financial aid from the FDIC. (Folder 15, Box 107)
  - Studies- Bank Records Project- Bibliography of source materials relating to American banking development. (Folder 107, Box 107)
  - Monetary Policy 1945-1962. (Folder 1, Box 108)
  - Mutual Savings Banks- Savings banks deposits insurance fund 1933-1962. (Folder 2, 3, Box 108)
  - NABAC Manual 1940-1943. (Folder 4, Box 108)
  - National Association of Bank Audit, Control and Operation. (Folder 5, Box 108)
  - National Association of Mutual Savings Banks 1934-1964. (Folder 6, Box 108)
  - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks 1934-1960. (Folder 7, Box 108)
  - Commercial Bank Urban Mortgage Loan Study- Correspondence and Memoranda 1946-1952. (Folder 8, Box 108)
  - Financial Research Program- Investment Standards(Corporate Bond Research Study). (Folder 9, Box 108)
    Also includes correspondence between National Bureau of Economic Research and Leo Crowley.
  - NBER 1935-1965. (Folder 10, Box 108)
  - New York Metropolitan Region Study 1957-1959. (Folder 11, Box 108)
  - Negro Banks 1943-1955. (Folder 12, Box 108)
  - Noninsured Banks 1941-1964. (Folder 13, Box 108)
  - Noninsured Banks- List of operating banks not insured by FDIC. (Folder 14, Box 108)
  - Miscellaneous. (Folder 15, Box 108)
  - Number of Operating Banks and Branches- Changes among operating banks 1935-1962. (Folder 1, Box 109)
  - Oil- Impact of oil discoveries, etc. 1952-1961. (Folder 2, Box 109)
  - Personnel- Memoranda 1956-1965, education and training, relations and welfare. (Folder 3-5, Box 109)
  - State Banking Authorities. (Folder 6, Box 109)
  - Pay-off- Receivership and absorption(Arkansas 1952, Illinois 1952, Pennsylvania). (Folder 7-9, Box 109)
  - Assets and Liabilities of All Banks- 1965, 1947-1962, FRS tables 1964. (Folder 10-12, Box 109)
  - Releases- Joint Statements of Supervising Agencies 1938-1962. (Folder 13, Box 109)
  - FDIC- Miscellaneous 1935-1954. (Folder 14, Box 109)
  - Survey of Insurance Coverage 1933-1965. (Folder 15, Box 109)
  - "Bank Capital: The problem restated" by Tynan Smith and Raymond E. Hengren. (Folder 16, Box 109)
  - A Broadened Program of Bank Reports 1936. (Folder 17, Box 109)
  - "Deposit Insurance as an Influence for Stabilizing the Banking Structure" by Mortimer J. Fox, 1936. (Folder 18, Box 109)
  - "Factors in Evaluation on Municipal Bonds" by Raymond E. Hengren, 1951. (Folder 19, Box 109)
  - "Going Concern Value in Bank Examination" by Harry L. Seversen, 1944. (Folder 20, Box 109)
  - Insurance of Commercial Bank Deposits by Carl F. Beherens. (Folder 21, Box 109)
  - Municipal Bonds in Bank Portfolios, 1951. (Folder 22, Box 109)
  - Bank Loans to Farmers- Commercial Bank Loans to Farmers 1947. (Folder 23, Box 109)
  - "Trends of Bank Earnings and Expenses" by Donald S. Thompson. (Folder 24, Box 109)
  - "Banking Market Structure and Performance in Metropolitan Areas" by Theodore G. Flechsig, 1965. (Folder 25, Box 109)
  - Real Estate- Real estate loans and other real estate, insured banks holdings of ORE, real estate mortgage loans in NY region. (Folder 26-28, Box 109)
  - Reciprocal Bank Balances. (Folder 29, Box 109)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation 1934-1950. (Folder 30, Box 109)
  - Records, Indispensable- Protection of FDIC records for emergency use. (Folder 31, Box 109)
  - Reference to FDIC- General, Encyclopedia Americana, Encyclopedia Britannica, Evening Bulletin Almanac, Federal Statistical Directory. (Folder 32-37, Box 109)
  - Reference to FDIC- Moody's Manuals, New International Year Book, U.S. Government Mannual. (Folder 1-3, Box 110)
  - Report of call, assets, and liabilities, etc. (Folder 4, Box 110)
  - Report form on interest rates and terms of savings and other time systems IPC. (Folder 5, Box 110)
  - Secretary of Defense. (Folder 6, Box 110)
  - Savings Banks Association (Folder 7, Box 110)
  - Reserve Requirements- Member banks reserve requirements. (Folder 8, Box 110)
  - General requests. (Folder 9, Box 110)
  - Securities- Miscellaneous, 1939-1963, Florida municipal obligations 1949-1954, Louisiana municipal obligations, municipal obligations as bank investments 1940, correspondence and memoranda, and amend to Securities Act of November 1941. (Folder 10-16, Box 110)
  - Senate- Correspondence 1934-1963. (Folder 17-20, Box 110)
  - Soviet Bloc Countries- Correspondence 1956-1963. (Folder 21, Box 110)
  - Speeches on FDIC, 1961. (Folder 22, Box 110)
  - State Banks Association 1960-1965. (Folder 23, Box 110)
  - State Banks Association 1953-1963. (Folder 24, Box 110)